sandiego6.com 2016-12-04

# Privacy Policy - CW6 San Diego

To participate in various activities on the Site, you will be asked to provide certain true, complete and current Personal Information or Sensitive Personal Information. All Personal Information, Sensitive Personal Information, and any additional type of information collected from users in general are subject to our Privacy Policy, which is incorporated by reference into this agreement. For more information, see our official Privacy Policy.

By submitting content to any area of the Site open to the other users or the general public (which includes, but is not limited to, contests, emails regarding Station programming, or Public Areas, you understand, acknowledge and agree that your content will be considered “Public Material” and will not be subject to the privacy protections generally afforded your Personal Information.

You further agree that the Site may save and archive any content of any nature posted to the Site and that the Site may, without liability to any user, disclose such content if required to do so by law or to comply with legal processes; to respond to claims that any of the content violates the property, privacy, publicity or any other rights of another individual, organization or corporation; or to protect the rights, property or safety of the Station, the Site, its corporate parents, affiliates, Advertisers, employees, suppliers, operational service providers, users and members of the public.

MODIFICATION, SUSPENSION OR DISCONTINUANCE OF SITE

The Site reserves the right, at its sole discretion and at any time, to modify or discontinue the service (or any part thereof) offered on the Site, on a temporary or permanent basis, with or without notice. You understand, acknowledge and agree that the Site will not be liable to you or to any third party for any such modification, suspension or discontinuance of the service offered by the Site.

SECURITY OF THE SITE

The Site’s loyal viewer/user and other membership activities are to be accessed only by registered users of the Site which should have only one unique user name with one unique password. If you are found to share passwords with any non-registered member we will terminate your membership immediately without notice.

As a user of this Site, the following actions are also prohibited:

1\. Accessing data not intended for such user or logging into a server or account in which the user is not authorized to access.

2\. Attempting to probe, scan or test the vulnerability of the system or network or to breach the security or authentication measures of the Site without proper authorization.

3\. Forging any headers or otherwise manipulation of Site identifiers in order to disguise the origin of transmission through the Site.

4\. Attempting to interfere with service to any user, host or network, including, without limitation, via means of submitting a virus to the Site, overloading, “flooding,” “spamming,” “mailbombing,” “spimming,” “phishing,” or “crashing” the Site or the server of any user.

5\. Sending unsolicited commercial email individually or in bulk (also called, Spam), which promotes or advertises the Station, the Site, or any other activity, program, product, or service.

6\. Harvesting email addresses off this Site through an automated process.

7\. Bypassing this Site’s homepage via deep-linking or any other means, or framing this Site, or any webpage or material on the Site without the express written permission from Bay City. Users are also prohibited from hyperlinking to this Site or any webpage in an email sent for commercial purposes, without the express written permission of Bay City.

8\. Attempting to gain unauthorized access to the Site’s features or activities, interfering with or manipulating in any manner the entry or registration process for contests, sweepstakes, surveys, opinion polls, chat rooms, message or bulletin boards, or any other interactive features and activities on this Site.

9\. Falsifying identification or impersonating any person or entity, including, but not limited to, a Site or Station official, chat room or public forum leader, host, or guide, when accessing or participating in such features and activities.

10\. Setting up fake sites or other dummy sites that appear to be the Site, mirroring the Site’s contents, or otherwise copying any part of the Site Material and/or layout.

Violations of the Site’s system or network security may result in civil or criminal liability. The Site will investigate possible violations of system or network security and may involve, and cooperate with a user’s employer, Internet Service Provider, and/or law enforcement authorities in investigating and/or prosecuting users who are involved in such violations. The Site will also terminate the membership of any person that the Site believes, in its sole judgment, to have violated its security provisions.

INDEMNIFICATION AND LIMITATION OF LIABILITY

You understand, acknowledge, and agree to defend, indemnify, and hold harmless Bay City Television Inc., its parent company(s), corporate affiliates, successors and assigns, Advertisers, suppliers and operational service providers and their respective officers, directors, stockholders, employees, representatives and agents, or others involved in creating, promoting, or otherwise making available this Site from and against any claims, actions, costs, expenses, or demands, including, without limitation, reasonable legal and accounting fees, resulting from any content you submit, post to or transmit through this Site, your use of the Site, your violation of this Agreement, your violation of any rights of another, or otherwise arising out of your use of this Site in any manner. The Site will attempt to provide notice to you promptly of any such claim, suit, or proceeding and will assist you, if requested and at your expense, in defending any such claim, suit or proceeding. We reserve the right to take exclusive control and defense of any such claim subject to indemnification by you, in which event you will cooperate fully with this Station in asserting any available defenses.

The Site and its Material may contain technical inaccuracies, typographical errors, and out of date information. The Site makes no representations about the accuracy, reliability, completeness, or timeliness of the Site or the Material, and the Site makes no warranty that the Site will meet your requirements. You understand, acknowledge, and agree that the use of the Site and the Material is at your own risk. The Site reserves the right to make changes to the Site and Material at any time.

IN NO EVENT SHALL THE SITE, ITS OWNER AND OPERATOR, PARENT COMPANY(S), CORPORATE AFFILIATES, SUCCESSORS OR ASSIGNS, AND THE SITE’S ADVERTISERS, SUPPLIERS, OR OPERATIONAL SERVICE PROVIDERS, AND THEIR RESPECTIVE OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, REPRESENTATIVES AND AGENTS, ASSUME OR HAVE ANY RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY FOR ANY CLAIMS, DAMAGES OR LOSSES WHATSOEVER INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, COMPENSATORY, PUNITIVE, EXEMPLARY OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, LOST PROFITS, OR DAMAGES RESULTING FROM LOST DATA, LOST SAVINGS, LOSS OF GOOD WILL, OR YOUR USE OR YOUR INABILITY TO USE THE SITE, OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION RESULTING FROM THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE THIS SITE, OR THE USE AND/OR APPEARANCE OF THE MATERIAL ON THIS SITE, ACCESS TO ANY HYPERLINK ON THIS SITE, UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO OR TAMPERING WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION OR TRANSMISSIONS, OR ANY OTHER INTANGIBLE, WHETHER BASED ON WARRANTY, CONTRACT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY, OR ANY OTHER LEGAL THEORY, AND WHETHER OR NOT THE COMPANY IS ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.

DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES

THE SITE DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE SITE WILL OPERATE ERROR-FREE OR THAT THE SITE AND ITS SERVER OR SOFTWARE IS FREE OF COMPUTER VIRUSES  
OR OTHER HARMFUL MECHANISMS. YOUR USE OF THE SITE IS UNDERTAKEN SOLELY AT YOUR DISCRETION AND OWN RISK. IF YOUR USE OF THE SITE, SOFTWARE, OR THE MATERIAL RESULTS IN THE NEED FOR SERVICING OR REPLACING EQUIPMENT OR DATA, YOU UNDERSTAND ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT THE SITE IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THOSE COSTS.

THE SITE AND MATERIAL ARE PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS” BASIS WITHOUT ANY WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND. THE SITE, TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION ANY WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON¬INFRINGEMENT. THE SITE MAKES NO WARRANTIES ABOUT THE ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, COMPLETENESS, OR TIMELINESS OF THE MATERIAL, SERVICES, SOFTWARE, DESIGN, TEXT, VIDEO CLIPS, AUDIO CLIPS, GRAPHICS AND ARTWORK, IMAGES, PHOTGRAPHS, OTHER MATERIAL, LINKS AND OTHER DATA.  
SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW FOR THE EXCLUSION OF CERTAIN WARRANTIES OR THE LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, AND SOME OF THE DISCLAIMERS IN THIS AGREEMENT MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU BY OPERATION OF LAW.

NOTWITHSTANDING ANY OTHER PROVISION OF THIS AGREEMENT, YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT THE AGGREGATE LIABILITY FOR THE COMPANY TO USERS FOR ALL CLAIMS ARISING FROM YOUR ACCESS, USE OR INABILITY TO ACCESS OR USE THIS SITE OR ANY OF THE MATERIAL OR SOFTWARE IS LIMITED TO $1.00 (ONE DOLLAR AND ZERO CENTS).

USER TERMINATION

The Site reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to terminate your membership or registration at any time, delete any or all of your Postings, or block access to the Site and/or any other service provided to you. The Site reserves the right to take such actions, with or without notice, for any reason or for no reason, and without any liability to the account holder or user.

LEGAL VENUE, GENERAL AND CONTACT INFORMATION

Except for matters related to copyright, trademark or patent, which shall be governed by U.S. federal law, this Agreement is governed by the internal substantive laws of the State of California, without respect to its conflict of laws provisions. Jurisdiction for any claims arising under this Agreement shall lie exclusively with the state or federal courts within California. You agree to submit to the personal jurisdiction of the courts in the State of California for any cause of action arising out of this Agreement.  
If any provision of this Agreement, or the application thereof to any person or circumstances, is found to be invalid or for any reason, unenforceable by any court having competent jurisdiction, the invalidity or unenforceability of such provision shall not affect the validity and application of the remaining provisions of this Agreement, which shall remain in full force and effect. No waiver of any term of this Agreement shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term or any other term. Except as expressly provided in this Agreement, in a particular “Legal Notice,” or Software License or material on particular Web pages, this Agreement constitutes the entire agreement between you and the Site with respect to the use of Site.

No changes to this Terms and Use Agreement shall be made except by a revised posting on this page and no advice or other information provided by the Site or its representatives to any user in any manner which is not posted on this page will constitute any amendment of, waiver or change to this Agreement, unless such an amendment, waiver or change is in writing from an authorized officer or representative of Bay City.

The section titles in this Agreement are for your convenience only and do not have any legal or contractual effect.

If you have any questions regarding this Agreement, please contact the Site’s Privacy Administrator via email at privacy@sandiego6.com or contact:

sandiego6.com, Bay City Television, Inc., 8253 Ronson Road, San Diego CA 92111

TM & © 2012 Bay City Television Inc. All Rights Reserved.

Privacy

This statement informs you of Bay City’s practices with respect to the online collection, use, and disclosure of personal information from this Bay City Website. Personal information is information that allows us to contact you (such as email address, home address, or telephone number) or other information that, when linked to your name or contact information, allows us to personalize your visit to our site by providing you with information that suits your interests. Bay City is the owner of this website and retains all ownership rights to the information collected at this site. Bay City reserves the right to change, modify, add, or remove provisions of this Privacy Statement. Any changes to this Privacy Statement will be posted here, and we encourage you to check back from time to time.

Personalization  
Although you may use many features of this site without completing a registration or sign-up form, visitors who do register and/or sign up for special services may have access to additional features of the site and are more likely to receive information suited to their interests. For example, a registered user is eligible for additional services provided by this website such as listener clubs and personalized content. Our registration and special services sign-up forms may ask you for contact information (like name or email address) and demographic information (like zip code or age). You must provide the information in order to receive the benefits of registration or of the special service.

We may use the contact information you give us to better tailor your website experience to your interests, and to send you information about Bay City and its services as well as promotional material on behalf of some of our partners. We use other information that you provide to us to show you content in which you may be interested and to display the content according to your preferences. We will also share this information within the Bay City family in order to enhance your experience on this and other Bay City Websites.

In addition, we may share this information with advertisers or other third parties that are not part of the Bay City family on an aggregate or other basis that does not disclose your identity or contact information.

Online Surveys/Contests  
From time to time, we may conduct online surveys and contests. These ask you for contact information (like name or email address) and demographic information (like zip code or age). We may use this contact information from our surveys and contests to provide you with information about our company and promotional material on behalf of some of our partners, and to contact you when necessary.

Supplemental Information  
To enhance Bay City’s ability to tailor this site to your preferences, we may combine information that you provide us on registration and other online sign-up forms with other information about you that we may obtain. We do not share that information with any other party.

Shopping/Commercial Services  
This Bay City site may offer shopping services, which may be offered by us or by a firm that operates a store under contract with us. If our site offers shopping or other commercial services, you will use a customer order form to request information, products, and services. The order form will ask you to give us contact information (like name or email address), financial information (like account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like zip code or age).

We will use the financial information that you provide to bill you for products and services. By giving our site your credit card and related personal information, you are authorizing our store to give that information to the merchant and credit card company in order to confirm and fulfill your order.

We will use contact information from the order form to fulfill your orders. We may also use contact data to get in touch with you when necessary. We will not otherwise use or distribute your financial information without your prior approval.

Public Forums  
This site may make available chat rooms, forums, message boards, and news groups. Please remember that any information that you disclose in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

Information Sharing With Third Parties  
From time to time we may enter into a special relationship with another company that is not owned by Bay City to provide additional features at this site. These special relationships may include “powered by” partners, business partners, sponsors, and co-branded sites (referred to here as “co-branded pages”). These might include, for example, pages that share our name and that of another entity, such as TicketMaster. You should look for a specific privacy statement on any such co-branded page. Any personal information that you provide when signing up at one of those co-branded pages may be shared with our third party partner. You should also check our partner’s website for information regarding its privacy policies.

Also, the nature of some features of our site may require that we share personal information about you with persons or companies outside of the Bay City family. For example, this may occur at a feature that enables you, via our site, to ask questions of persons or entities that are not part of the Bay City family. By responding to those features of the site, whether by email or direct entry of information on our Website, you are consenting to our transferring that information to such persons or entities.

With respect to specific registration modules, like contests, we may disclose personal information collected, and we will post a conspicuous statement on the registration module to the effect that we will be disclosing the information collected with third parties

Finally, we may share any of the information collected from you with these other non-Bay City companies in an aggregate basis. The aggregated information is not linked to any information that can identify you.

IP Address and Log Files  
We may use your IP address to administer our Website, to help diagnose problems with our server, to analyze trends, to track users’ webpage movements, to help identify you and your shopping cart, and to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

Cookies  
This Bay City site may use a standard technology called a “cookie” to collect information about how you use the site. Cookies reside on your computer and help our website to recognize your computer’s browser as a previous visitor. This information allows us to customize delivery of information. For example, our site may use cookies to save and remember registration information or preferences that you may have set while browsing the site, to keep track of your shopping cart, to ensure you don’t see the same ad content repeatedly, to deliver content specific to your interests, and to save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. We use cookies only to gather information as indicated in this policy. In addition, on occasion our site may also set a “session cookie” which helps us administer the site. The session cookie expires when you close your browser and does not retain any information about you after it expires.

Finally, we may also use an ad network provider to help present advertisements on this and other Bay City Web sites. This ad network provider, like other advertising service vendors, uses cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies on the hard drive of your computer to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, and to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. In doing so, the provider collects non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by these ad network providers is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours. If you do not want the benefits of these advertising cookies, you may opt-out by visiting http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp. However, if you do so you may not receive the full benefit from the use of our site.

Banner Advertising  
We license ad-server software from another company to place banner advertising on our sites. All of the data provided and generated by the ad-server software remains in our possession and no data is transferred to the licensor of the software. This feature of our site may, on occasion, set “cookies” on your computer. Any information collected or stored by the ad-service or the cookies is treated in the same manner as other information as described in this statement. Children’s Personal Information  
Consistent with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act:

• This site does NOT collect, use, or disclose personal information (including online contact information) of children under the age of 13.

• In the event that a child under the age of 13 attempts to register on our site, we will NOT accept the registration and will delete information received from the child.

• In the event that a child posts personal information in a public forum such as a chat room, we will attempt to delete that information once we become aware of it.

Your Choices  
This Bay City site provides you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving email communications from us and our special relationship partners. To opt-out of receiving email communications, you may:

• Modify your registered user information on our website at www.sandiego6.com/enews/signup

Access to Personal Information  
Bay City gives you the opportunity to modify or remove personal information that you have provided to us. You may do so by modifying your password-protected registered user information on our website.

Security of Your Personal Information  
Bay City employs reasonable security measures consistent with standard industry practice, for information collected through this website. We believe that we have adequate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of the information we collect on our website. We also use internal protections to limit access to users’ personal information to only those employees who need the information to perform a specific job.

Sale or Merger  
If this site is sold to, or merges with, another company not owned by Bay City, you should expect that some or all of the information collected from this website may be transferred to the buyer/surviving company. If so, Bay City will seek to obligate the acquiring company to use any personal information transferred by this site in a manner consistent with this statement, but cannot guarantee that it will be able to impose that requirement or that the acquiring company will comply.

Legal Process  
You should be aware that Bay City may be required to disclose your personal information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, such as in court or regulatory proceedings.

Leased Content  
Neither Standard & Poor nor any third-party licensor shall have any liability for the accuracy or completeness of this service or any component thereof or for delays, unauthenticity, omissions, or other defects therein nor for any claims or losses arising therefrom or occasioned thereby, including, without limitation, any lost profits, indirect, special, or consequential damages. Either Standard & Poor or third party licensors have exclusive proprietary rights from the information received via the service. Customer, end-user, or visitor, as applicable, shall not use or permit anyone to use the information provided through the service for any unlawful or unauthorized purpose. Customer, end-user, or visitor, as applicable, is not authorized or permitted to furnish such information to any person or firm for reuse or retransmission without prior written approval of the source of such information. Provision of the information on the service is subject to termination in the event that any agreement between a third party licensor and a provider of information distributed through the service is terminated in accordance with its terms. Third party licensor and its subsidiaries, affiliates, information providers and content partners shall have no liability for investment decisions based on the information provided hereby.

General Information  
This Agreement and the Additional Terms shall be governed by, construed and enforced in accordance with the laws of the State of Texas, as it is applied to agreements entered into and to be performed entirely within such state, without regard to conflict of law principles. You agree that any cause of action you or Bay City brings to enforce this Agreement and/or the Additional Terms, or in connection with any matters related to this Bay City Website and/or the Privacy Statement, shall be brought only in either the state or Federal courts located in San Diego, California . You agree to submit to the personal jurisdiction of the courts of the State of California for any cause of action arising out of this Agreement. You agree to file any cause of action with respect to this Agreement within one year after the cause of action arises. You agree that a cause of action filed after this date is barred.

If any provision of this Agreement, or the application thereof to any person or circumstances, is held invalid or for any reason, unenforceable including, but not limited to, the warranty disclaimers and liability limitations, then such provision shall be deemed superseded by a valid, enforceable provision that matches, as closely as possible, the original provision, and the other provisions of this Agreement shall remain in full force and effect. The failure of either party to insist upon strict performance of any provision of this Agreement shall not be construed as a waiver of any provision or right. Unless expressly provided otherwise, this Agreement is the entire agreement between you and Bay City with respect to the use of this Bay City Website and shall not be modified except in writing, signed by an authorized representative of Bay City.

European Union and Other Foreign Nations  
This Bay City website is governed by and operated in accordance with the laws of United States of America and is intended for enjoyment of residents of the United States. Bay City makes no representation that this website is governed by or operated in accordance with the laws of other nations. By using this site and submitting any personal information, visitors from outside of the United States acknowledge the this site is subject to U.S. law, consent to the transfer of personal data to the U.S., and waive any claims that may arise under their own national laws.

Copyright & Trademark Notice

Use of Intellectual Property  
The Bay City Website, and all of its contents, including but not limited to articles, other text, photographs, images, illustrations, graphics, video material, audio material, including musical compositions and sound recordings, software, Bay City logos, titles, characters, names, graphics and button icons (collectively “Intellectual Property”), are protected by copyright, trademark and other laws of the United States, as well as international conventions and the laws of other countries. The Intellectual Property is owned or controlled by Bay City or by other parties that have provided rights thereto to Bay City.

You may not, and agree that you will not, reproduce, download, license, publish, enter into a database, display, modify, create derivative works from, transmit, post, distribute or perform publicly by any means, method, or process now known or later developed, decompile, reverse engineer, disassemble, use on another computer-related environment, transfer or sell any Intellectual Property, information, software or products obtained from or through this Bay City Website, in whole or in part, without the express written permission of Bay City.

Other trademarks, service marks, product names and company names or logos appearing on this Bay City Website that are not owned by Bay City may not be used without express permission from their owners.

Additionally, unless otherwise expressly permitted, websites may not hyperlink to any page beyond the homepage of this Bay City Website, or frame this Bay City Website, or any web page or material herein, nor may any entity include a hyperlink to any aspect of the Bay City Website in an email for commercial purposes, without the express written permission of Bay City.

Copyright Infringement  
Bay City respects the intellectual property rights of third parties, and complies with the terms of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA) regarding such rights. By submitting any material or photographs through this Bay City Website, you are granting permission to have this material posted on this Bay City Website, and are representing that you are the rightful owner of the submitted material, and that no one else may claim rights to this material. Bay City reserves the right to remove access to infringing material. Such actions do not affect or modify any other rights Bay City may have under law or contract. You can find our procedures for providing notice of alleged copyright infringement here.

Pursuant to 17 U.S.C. § 512(c), to be effective, the Notification must include the following:

(i) A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.

(ii) Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed, or, if multiple copyrighted works at a single online site are covered by a single notification, a representative list of such works at that site.

(iii) Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled, and information reasonably sufficient to permit Bay City to locate the material.

(iv) Information reasonably sufficient to permit Bay City to contact the complaining party, such as an address, telephone number, and, if available, an email address.

(v) A statement that the complaining party has a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law.

(vi) A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.

This process only relates to reporting a claim of copyright infringement. Messages related to other matters will not receive a response through this process.

Privacy Policy  
and Your California Privacy Rights

Welcome to www.sandiego6.com (“Site”, “us” or “we”), the official website for television station San Diego 6 (XETV-TV) San Diego, CA (hereinafter, “Site”). This Site is owned and operated by Bay City Television, Inc.

We take your privacy seriously. Because we gather certain types of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) from users of our website and for various Station activities, operational and business purposes, we feel you should know how we collect, use, disclose, manage, and store the Personal Information that you may voluntarily provide to us and the Personal Information that may be collected passively through the use of cookies or image tags on our website.

This Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference in the Site’s Terms of Use Agreement, which is binding on all Site users. This Policy applies only to the Personal Information collected by this Station and does not govern any such information collected by its corporate parent(s), affiliates, or any other company, unless specifically stated.

Please do not participate in the Station’s online or off-line activities and services that may require you to provide your Personal Information if you do not agree with this Privacy Policy. This Policy provides information regarding your choice to Opt-out of receiving informational, promotional and marketing communications from the Station and its affiliated entities.  
YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

Residents of the State of California that have an established business relationship with a company that conducts business in California, under a provision of the California Civil Code, have the right to request from that company a list of all third parties to which the company has disclosed Personal Information about the resident during the preceding year for direct marketing purposes. Alternatively, the law provides that if the company has a privacy policy that gives either an Opt-out or Opt-in choice for use of Personal Information by third parties (such as advertisers or certain affiliated companies) for marketing purposes, the company may instead provide you with information on how to exercise your disclosure choice options.

This Station qualifies for the alternative option; it has a comprehensive privacy policy and provides you with details on how you may Opt-out or Opt-in to the use of your Personal Information by third parties for direct marketing purposes. Therefore, we are not required to maintain or disclose a list of the third parties that received your Personal Information for direct marketing purposes during the preceding year.

If you are a California resident and have an established business relationship with us and want to receive information about how to exercise your third party disclosure choices you must send a request to the following address with a preference on how our response to your request should be sent (email or postal mail). You may contact us in two ways. Send email to Privacy Administrator at privacy@sandiego6.com. Alternatively, you may contact the Station at:  
San Diego 6 (XETV-TV) San Diego  
Bay City Television  
8253 Ronson Road  
San Diego CA 92111  
Attn: Your California Privacy Rights

c/o Privacy Administrator

For requests sent via email, you must put the statement “Your California Privacy Rights” in the subject field of your email. All requests sent via postal mail must be labeled “Your California Privacy Rights” on the envelope or post card and clearly stated on the actual request. For all requests, please include your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. (Your street address is optional if you wish to receive a response to your request via email. Please include your zip code for our own recordkeeping.) We will not accept requests via the telephone or by facsimile. We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information.

To all other users of this Site, if you have other questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact our Privacy Administrator at the following email address: privacy@sandiego6.com or:  
San Diego 6 (XETV-TV) San Diego  
Bay City Television  
8253 Ronson Road  
San Diego CA 92111  
Attn: Privacy Administrator  
GENERAL PRIVACY GUIDELINES

Unless specified otherwise on the Site, all users must be at least 18 years of age and a legal resident of the United States to participate in any activity that requires the submission of Personal Information. This Site is designed and targeted to United States (U.S.) audiences and is governed by and operated in accordance with the laws of the United States. We make no representation that this Site is operated in accordance with the laws or governed by other nations. By your participation in our Site activities, you certify that you are at least 18 years of age and a legal resident in the U.S. If you are located in the European Union or elsewhere outside of the U.S. and you participate in activities on this Site contrary to our policy that only U.S. residents are eligible for certain activities, you do so at your own risk and initiative, and are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. Please be aware that any Personal Information you transfer to us will be transferred to the U.S and subject to U.S. law. By using this Site, participating in any Site activities, and/or providing us with your Personal Information, you consent to this transfer of Personal Information to the U.S., and waive any claims that may arise under your own national laws.

All users of the Site are required to provide true, current, complete and accurate Personal Information when prompted. We will reject and delete any entry that we believe in good faith to be false, fraudulent, or inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

Your continued participation on this Site indicates your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and of the collection, use, disclosure, management and storage of your Personal Information as described below. We may from time to time transfer or merge any Personal Information collected off-line to our online databases or store off-line information in an electronic format. We may also combine Personal Information we collect online with information available from other sources, including information received from our corporate affiliates, advertisers, or marketing companies.

This Privacy Policy covers all such Personal Information and will remain in full force and effect as long as you are a user of the Site or a participant in Station activities. We reserve the right to revise this policy at any time by updating this posting without advance notice to you. Such revisions shall be effective to you immediately upon posting. Therefore, we encourage you to check this Privacy Policy often.

We use your Personal Information to provide you with the features, services, or goods you request and to respond to questions related to the Station or Site. We will also use your Personal Information to notify you about updates, new features, programming and activities on behalf of the Station or Site that may be of interest to you.

We may also use your information for hiring, operational and business purposes, or to find out how we can improve our Station and Site via surveys or online tracking mechanisms. We use aggregate Personal Information to help us to evaluate and modify existing services and features. We also use your Personal Information to develop new services and features that may be of interest to you.

We will not sell, exchange, rent, lease or otherwise disclose your Personal Information or Sensitive Personal Information (as defined below), to other third party marketers or advertisers or any persons that are not associated with the Station unless it is necessary to: 1) conform to regulatory and legal requirements or to comply with the legal process; 2) to protect the safety and security of our users, employees, or property; 3) to defend the rights of the Site or the Station; or 4) to enforce the Terms of Use Agreement.

We will share your Personal Information with our corporate parents and affiliated entities primarily for business and operational purposes. On occasion, we will share your Personal Information with our affiliated corporate entities for promotional and marketing purposes.

It is also necessary that we share your Personal Information and Sensitive Personal Information with our operational service providers, the specialists that provide internal support to Station operations and activities and/or for Site design, development, hosting and operations including maintenance, management, storage and/or fulfillment of our membership and e-mail clubs, various contests, sweepstakes, services, events and online stores. We use operational service providers to efficiently provide the full range of content, activities and membership services we bring to you and we request that our operational service providers also protect your privacy and not disclose your Personal Information or Sensitive Personal Information to third party marketers that are not associated with the Station or Site. Additionally, such providers are not to use your Personal Information or Sensitive Personal Information for their own marketing or promotional purposes.

In the event that the assets or stock of the Station, its corporate licensee or parent company(s) are sold or transferred, merged with a different company or entity, restructured, or subject to other fundamental corporate changes, we reserve the right to disclose any and all databases compiled from Personal Information or Sensitive Personal Information collected by the Station to such successor. We will seek to obligate the Station’s successor to agree to the terms of the Privacy Policy, as it may hereafter be modified, but cannot guarantee that we will be able to do so or that the successor company will comply with this obligation.

We reserve the right to collect Personal Information using any new technology yet to be developed and to use such technology to provide new services and features to you, as well as for marketing and promotional purposes. Specific information regarding your choice to Opt-in or to Opt-out to such use, or for sharing your Personal Information with advertisers, will be provided once the new technology, service, or feature is introduced.

WEBSITE COLLECTION, USE, AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Generally, you may browse this Site, and watch clips of our programs, without providing any Personal Information. For certain activities (which may include, but is not limited to, contest and sweepstakes registrations, membership, viewer clubs, surveys and news/sports/weather alerts) the Personal Information you voluntarily provide may include your first/middle and last name, home address, business address, email address, telephone number, mobile phone/text messaging device number, birth date, gender, employer or personal preferences, depending on the activity.

Unless stated otherwise, we do not request contact information for a mobile phone, text messaging or any wireless device that includes a domain name address (such as “.net” or “.com”) as part of the contact information. Federal law prohibits the sending of commercial email messages directly to a wireless device that uses a domain name, unless you have first given your affirmative consent. We may inadvertently collect a wireless device number that includes a domain name when you send us an inquiry or register for a contest or membership club. However, we will not knowingly use that contact information for sending commercial email. We reserve the right to respond to user inquiries or requests sent via a wireless device that uses a domain name as such messages are not deemed to be commercial email and therefore, are not regulated by Federal law. However, when “computer to phone” commercial emails are prohibited by law, we may reject your wireless device contact information when such information is submitted for certain Site features or services. We will attempt to notify you if we will need new contact information.

For specific purposes (such as the purchase of goods and services) we may request a type of confidential personally identifiable information which shall be called “Sensitive Personal Information” and is defined as any individual’s: (1) social security number; (2) driver’s license number or state identification card number; (3) account number, credit or debit card number, with or without any required security code, access code or password that would permit access to an individual’s financial account; (4) mother’s maiden name; (5) passport number; or (6) electronic or digitized signature. Sensitive Personal Information will only be used to implement the specific activity or event it was submitted for. We will not share your Sensitive Personal Information with advertisers.

However, more general Personal Information will be used to implement the specific activity or event and will also be used for the marketing of additional events, services and merchandising for this Site and the Station.

DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Advertising support allows us to offer, free of charge, many great activities and services to our users such as contests, membership clubs, sweepstakes and special events. However, we do not currently share Personal Information with our advertisers. However, depending on the activity, we may in the future do so and you will receive notice on the Site and/or in the rules of participation (“Rules of Participation”) for the event or activity, or via an email notice. Please be informed that our advertisers may not have the same privacy policies that we do. Therefore, you will need to tell us if you do not want to receive marketing information directly from our advertisers. You will need to check the “Opt-out” click boxes that may be included in the registration area for the particular event, in an email, or alternatively, notify the Site’s Privacy Administrator at privacy@sandiego6.com. You will also need to tell us if you do not wish to receive marketing or promotional materials from the Site and/or Station in the same manner.

We also provide you with an option to “Opt-out” of receiving advertising and promotional email from us in compliance with federal law by installing an Opt-out mechanism with all such email messages. You must use the designated method in the email message to notify us of your Opt-out request, as we cannot guarantee that other methods of notification will be effective or timely. Please be aware that we may continue to contact you via email for administrative or informational purposes, including follow-up messages regarding contests you have entered or other transactions you have undertaken. By law, such messages are not considered to be commercial email.

We are not responsible for removing your Personal Information from third party lists or entities which you have previously authorized us to share your information. You will need to contact those entities directly.

COOKIES AND IMAGE TAGS

The use of cookies is an industry standard and they are currently used on most websites, including this Site. Cookies are a small text file containing a unique identification number that is transferred from a website to the hard drive of a user’s computer so that the website administrator or a third party operational service provider may identify the computer and passively track the user’s activities on the website. Image tags work in conjunction with cookies and are small image files that may be located on select pages of our Site, or within web-based email newsletters that we may send. (Image tags are also called web beacons, web bugs, clear GIFs or single-pixel GIFs.). Tracking is important because we can better understand which parts of our website are used the most, when to launch new services and how to enhance current offerings. We may share the information we receive from cookies and image tags with third-parties and our advertisers in aggregate form, which means that such information does not contain specific Personal Information or Sensitive Personal Information about any one visitor.

In short, cookies and image tags collect a user’s Internet protocols and server information. Such data files will allow our Site to remember your web browser when you visit our Site and will allow for quick and efficient access to our many services. A cookie will not allow the Site to learn any Personal Information (such as your real name and email address) or Sensitive Personal Information that you have not otherwise disclosed. Cookies and image tags allow the Site to remember important information that will make the Site easier for you to use and helpful in our administration of various activities. We do not use cookies or image tags to collect other Personal Information or Sensitive Personal Information unless you give us permission to do so.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie or image tag is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all such devices. This is done through your browser. If you turn cookies off, you may not then have access to many features at our Site that make your Internet experience more efficient and enjoyable – like the features mentioned above – and some of our other services will not function properly.

CHILDREN’S PRIVACY POLICY

Although persons of all ages may visit our Site and participate in activities that do not require the collection of Personal Information or Sensitive Personal Information, we do not knowingly or intentionally collect Personal Information or Sensitive Personal Information from children under the age of 13. Except for the limited circumstances listed below, we will automatically reject and delete the registration or entry of any person we believe in good faith to be underage. Any false or fraudulent registration or entry from a minor will be deemed to be ineligible and will disqualify the minor from the receipt of a prize, benefit, or other participation.

Except to meet Federal Communications Commission (“FCC”), or other regulatory and legal purposes, we will not use, store, or disclose any child’s Personal Information to a third party without prior parental consent.

EMAIL

Any communications or materials sent to the Station or Site by any user via email or otherwise, including any comments, data, questions, suggestions or the like, will be treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary. You agree that any use of such material does not violate any rights including, but not limited to, privacy rights, proprietary or other property rights, publicity rights, rights to credit for material or ideas, including the right to approve the way the Station uses such material. Any material submitted to us or the Site may be adapted, broadcast, changed, copied, disclosed, licensed, performed, posted, published, sold or transmitted by the Station anywhere in the world, through any medium now known or later devised.

We do not generally keep email correspondence sent to the Site. Please do not place any Sensitive Personal Information in your email correspondence to the Station that pertains to station programming or operations.

SHOPPING & E-COMMERCE

If this Site sells goods and/or services we will request Sensitive Personal Information that includes your credit card, debit card or other payment information. Alternatively, the Site may use a third party operational service provider to conduct the financial transaction in a secured manner; the third party payment will be accessible via a hyperlink from the Site and will be solely responsible for all financial transactions and the collection, use, and storage of your Personal Information and Sensitive Personal Information. We may request additional Personal Information such as full name, billing and shipping address, email address and telephone number and any such information that is required to fulfill your order and to communicate with you regarding your order. Sensitive Personal Information will be encrypted or collected though a secured Internet connection generally via SSL or S-HTTP protocols. Such Sensitive Personal Information will also be stored in a commercially reasonable secure manner. We may use your Personal Information, (but not your credit card or debit card number) to contact you about future products, services and discounts from the Station unless you tell us otherwise (“Opt-out”). We will only use your credit card and debit card number to complete the specific transaction you requested.

CHAT ROOMS, MESSAGE BOARDS AND PUBLIC AREAS

For your enjoyment and entertainment, this Site may choose to offer user interactive activities such as chat rooms, message boards, and/or public forums (“Public Areas”). We will not share any Personal Information or Sensitive Personal Information that is entered into the Public Area registration section on the Site with advertisers.

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to save and archive any content of any nature posted to the Site and that we may, without liability to any user: 1) disclose such content if required to do so by law or to comply with legal processes; 2) to respond to claims that any of the content violates the property, privacy, publicity or other rights of others; or 3) to protect the rights, property or safety of the Site, the Station, its employees, users and members of the public.

MONITORING AND USE OF AGGREGATE PERSONAL INFORMATION

We reserve the right to monitor and edit any Personal Information about our users, including information about the use of website activities and services, the contents of users’ email and messages for internal purposes, and when necessary, to disclose to law enforcement personnel, and/or the employer and/or Internet Service Provider of a user that is not in compliance with the Terms of Use Agreement or Privacy Policy. We will take such measures if we believe it is necessary to protect the security, integrity, and operations of this Site or Station. Without disclosure of Personal Information or Sensitive Personal Information about individual users, we may provide aggregate statistics about our users, traffic patterns and related website information to advertisers, reputable third party vendors or marketing companies.

ADVERTISING AND OTHER THIRD PARTY CONTENT

This Privacy Policy does not cover third party advertising or third party content that may be present on the Site. This Site may provide banner and general advertising, in addition to other content provided by our advertisers or operational service providers. Users may from time to time purchase goods or services offered through, or otherwise participate in or send messages concerning such advertising, promotions or third party content offered through the Site. Such correspondence, transactions and agreements are solely between the user and the Advertiser or the third party content provider and do not involve the Site. Also, advertisers and such third party content providers may not have the same privacy policies that we do and you are encouraged to read their privacy policy first.

PHISHING

Phishing attacks attempt to steal consumers’ personal identity data and financial account credentials. “Phishers” use ‘spoofed’ e-mails to lead consumers to counterfeit websites designed to trick recipients into divulging Sensitive Personal Information such as credit card numbers, account usernames, passwords and social security numbers. We will NEVER send an email asking you to provide or confirm Sensitive Personal Information. If you receive a communication such as this, please immediately forward it to the Site’s Privacy Administrator at privacy@sandiego6.com, and immediately delete it from your computer.

HYPERLINKS TO, AND FRAMING OF, OTHER WEBSITES

This Site often provides links to third party websites that could be of interest to our users, including the websites of our advertisers. As stated in our Terms of Use Agreement, the Station does not own or control these websites and therefore, is not responsible for the content, business practices, or operations of such websites. Third party websites linked or framed on this Site may have different privacy policies and business practices than we do. The presence of a link to a third party website does not constitute or imply our endorsement, recommendation, or sponsorship of the third party content, goods, or services available through, or contained on, the Site. By use of this Site, you have agreed that you will use the hyperlinks to third party sites at your own risk.

OFF-LINE COLLECTION, USE, AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

The Station also collects and uses Personal Information by other means, via on-air broadcasts, telephone, direct mail, and direct communications from members of the public. The various uses of such Personal Information may include, but are not limited to, contests and sweepstakes, loyal viewer club registration, other special membership only features/events, news tip lines, job applications, viewer complaints, and operational and business purposes.  
Except for contests and sweepstakes entries, or registrations for a loyal viewer or other special membership features/events, we do not ordinarily use your Personal Information collected off-line for promotional or advertising purposes, nor do we share it with third parties for promotional or marketing purposes. If Personal Information collected off-line will be used by the Station, its parent company(s), or corporate affiliates for promotional and marketing purposes, you have the opportunity to Opt-out of such use.

SECURITY MEASURES

We conduct the collection, management, maintenance and storage of viewer or website user information in a secure and commercially reasonable manner using acceptable industry standards of security technology and practices (such as electronic security systems and password protections) to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of Personal Information. We also request that our operational service providers take such precautions. The Station’s databases are accessible only by authorized personnel.

However, please note that when users transmit Personal Information over an unsecured Internet connection, the Site is not responsible for the security of that information during the transmission stage as your email or registration could be copied or intercepted by unknown third parties. We use a secured connection only for the collection of Sensitive Personal Information, which is necessary for the purchase of goods or services, but we do not use a secured connection for other types of activities. Therefore, you understand, acknowledge, and agree that you transmit certain Personal Information to this Site at your own risk.

REVIEW, UPDATE, CORRECT, OR DELETE PERSONAL INFORMATION OR SENSITIVE PERSONAL INFORMATION

Generally, you may review, update or delete your Personal Information or Sensitive Personal Information collected by the Site. You may also correct factual inaccuracies. Certain types of Personal Information that are necessary to check eligibility, such as birth date or age, cannot be deleted, but may be modified with sufficient verification of the new information. Note that we reserve the right to terminate or delete any membership or entry if we believe the Personal Information submitted was knowingly false or fraudulent.

To review, update or delete your Personal Information or Sensitive Personal Information collected by the Site, please email the Site’s Privacy Administrator at privacy@sandiego6.com or click here. To have access to your Personal Information or Sensitive Personal Information, you must provide proof of identification such as full name, street address, city/state and zip code, user ID and password, and/or information about your recent activity on the website. We reserve the right to deny access to any user if we believe there is a question about your identity. And if the burden or expense of providing access to your Personal Information is disproportionate to the risks to your privacy, or if the legitimate rights of others would be violated, we may decide not to provide access to such information. In such cases, we will provide to you with an explanation of why access cannot be provided and a contact person for further inquiries.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on January 25, 2012 and is effective immediately.

TM & © 2012 Bay City Television Inc. All Rights Reserved.

o.
